resales-online.com 2018-09-29

# Real Estate Software | CRM Software | Rental Software | Spain

**In compliance with Law 34/2002 LSSICE, of June 11, 2002, on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce, we inform you that this website is wholly owned and administered by ReSales Andalucia SL, and this Legal Notice & Privacy Policy sets out how we will use and protect any information that you give us when you use this website. **

**ReSales Andalucia SL is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.**

**By accepting this Legal Notice & Privacy Policy you are consenting to and accepting the terms laid out in this policy. **

**USERS WHO DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY MUST NOT INTRODUCE ANY DATA BY MEANS OF THIS WEBSITE OR ACCESS THE CONTENT OF THIS WEBSITE.**

* * *

##  **Who we are**

References in this Legal Notice & Privacy Policy to â€œReSales Andaluciaâ€, â€œReSales Onlineâ€, â€œPropExtraâ€, â€œweâ€, â€œusâ€, â€œourâ€, or â€œourselvesâ€ relate to ReSales Andalucia SL a company registered in Spain with offices at Avenida Condes de San Isidro, 9, 1st Floor, Office 11, 29640 Fuengirola (MÃ¡laga) and at CC Guadalmina 4, Edif 2, Local 86, 29670 San Pedro de Alcantara (MÃ¡laga). ReSales Andalucia SL with CIF number B92950096 was constituted before the Public Notary Mr Ricardo Rincon Salas of Marbella on 7th July 2008, Protocol 746, inscribed in the Mercantile Register of MÃ¡laga, Volume 4544, Book 3453, Folio 195, Page MA-98.255.

When you enter your personal data into this website you are the â€œData Subjectâ€. We control the ways your personal data is collected and the purposes for which your personal data is used by ReSales Andalucia, acting as the â€œData Controllerâ€ for the purposes of applicable European data protection legislation.

##  **Purpose of the processing of personal data**

In accordance with the provisions of the Personal Data Protection Act and EU Regulation 2016/679, in the event that you send us an e-mail to the address indicated therein, or fill in any data collection form, we inform you that the personal data you provide will be registered in the file for which ReSales Andalucia is responsible, for the purposes described in this Legal Notice & Privacy Policy.

##  **Security**

ReSales Andalucia declares that it has adopted all the necessary and appropriate security measures in accordance with the provisions of EU Regulation 2016/679 and Royal Decree 1720/2007, of 21 December, approving the Regulation implementing the LOPD and has established all the technical means at its disposal with the intention of preventing the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorised access or theft of the data you provide.

Notwithstanding the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal information; however, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information entered on our website. When you enter your information on our website this is done at your own risk.

When you have registered an account to use our website and selected an access password, you are solely responsible for keeping the confidentiality of your login details. Please donâ€™t share your password with anyone.

##  **Cookie policy - how we use them**

In compliance with Law 34/2002 on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce LSSICE and its amendments of Royal Decree-Law 13/2012 of 30 March, which affect the use of cookies and commercial e-mails, and in compliance with European Directive 2009/136/EC, and in order to ensure your privacy, we inform you that we use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computerâ€™s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

##  **What we collect from you**

We will collect information that you provide to us when you complete a form on our website, either to register for:

  * an account to use the PropExtra website (www.propextra.com) 

  * or to register your interest in a property on the PropExtra website (www.propextra.com) website with the intention to contact the estate agent that listed the property 

  * an account to use our software ReSales Online (www.resales-online.com). 

This information may include:

  * Your name 

  * Your company name 

  * Address 

  * Contact information including telephone number and email address 

  * Fiscal information for invoicing purposes (ReSales Online Network and Standalone accounts) 

  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers. 

We may also collect information about you when you visit our website, including your IP address and information about your browsing history and how you use our site during your visit. This information may be combined with other information you provide to us, as described above.

##  **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * So that we can provide you with the information and services that you request from us. 

  * Maintain a business relationship in the case of commercial accounts. 

  * Administration of our website, including business administration and record keeping, troubleshooting, testing, research, data analysis, statistical and survey purposes. 

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services to enhance your experience on our website. 

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers, competitions, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

In accordance with the provisions of the Personal Data Protection Act and EU Regulation 2016/679, in the event that you send us an e-mail to the address indicated therein, or fill in any data collection form, we inform you that the personal data you provide will be registered in the file for which ReSales Andalucia SL is responsible, for the purposes described above.

##  **Sharing your personal information**

We may share your personal information with a third party for the following reasons:

  * When you complete an Inquiry Form on the PropExtra website (www.propextra.com) to enquire about a property, the personal information that you provide will be passed on to the estate agent that listed the property on the website. Once your personal information has been passed on to the relevant third party estate agent, they will be responsible for the way they use your information, protecting its secrecy and will be governed by their own terms of use and privacy policy. 

  * If we are under a duty to disclose your personal information in order to comply with a legal obligation, or in order to enforce our terms of use; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our website, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection. 

  * We will not sell or lease your personal information. 

  * In the case that you sign up for a commercial account (ReSales Online Network Account), your company trading name, address and contact email and telephone number(s) will be displayed on the ReSales Online Membership List which is only accessible by other ReSales Online member agents. This information is shared for the purpose of facilitating contact between member agents in their activity as estate agents. 

##  **Personal data of third parties**

In the event that the personal data provided belonged to a third party, the User guarantees that he or she has informed this third party of this Privacy Policy and has obtained his or her authorization to provide his or her data to ReSales Andalucia for the above purposes. Likewise, it guarantees that the information provided is accurate and up to date, and it is liable for any direct or indirect damage or injury that may be caused as a result of non-compliance with this obligation.

##  **Period of storage of personal data**

The personal data provided will be kept for as long as the contractual relationship is maintained, the data subject does not request its deletion and should not be deleted as necessary for the fulfilment of a legal obligation or for the formulation, exercise and defence of claims.

If the User revokes his/her consent or exercises the rights of cancellation or suppression, his/her personal data will be kept at the disposal of the Administration of Justice for the legally established periods in order to meet the possible responsibilities arising from the processing of the same.

##  **Legitimate interest for the processing of personal data**

ReSales Andalucia is entitled to carry out the processing of personal data on the basis that:

  * You have provided your personal data for pre-contractual or contractual relations. 

  * You have given your informed consent for the sending of commercial communications, for the installation of tracking systems that report on browsing habits according to the Cookies Policy, or for the sending of information required through contact forms. 

  * If there are legal obligations that require the processing of personal data, in accordance with the services provided. 

##  **Transfers and recipients of personal data**

For the fulfillment of the above-mentioned purposes or in compliance with legal obligation, personal data may be transferred to:

  * Public Administrations and the Administration of Justice. 

  * IT service providers, including 'cloud computing' services. 

##  **Rights of Data Subjects**

You can contact ReSales Andalucia to exercise your rights of access, rectification or erasure, limitation of their processing, opposition, portability, and to object to automated individual decisions. Likewise,you may revoke your consent if you have granted it for a specific purpose, and may modify your preferences at any time.

You can do this by via letter to ReSales Online, Customer Services Team, Avenida Condes de San Isidro, 9, 1st Floor, Office 11, 29640 Fuengirola (MÃ¡laga) or via email to gdpr@resales-online.es.

Users are informed that they may address any type of complaint regarding personal data protection to the Spanish Data Protection Agency www.agpd.es, the Spanish State Control Authority.

##  **ReSales Online software system**

If you use or are planning to use our ReSales Online software, in conjunction with this Legal Notice and Privacy Policy, you should also read and agree to the following:

  * ReSales Online service prices [ https://www.resales-online.com/en/pricing.html ](https://www.resales-online.com/en/pricing.html)

  * Terms & Conditions of Software Usage which include our Data Protection Agreement between ReSales Andalucia (â€œData Processorâ€) and estate agents that subscribe to use our ReSales Online software (â€œData Controllersâ€). [ https://www.resales-online.com/en/terms-and-conditions.html ](https://www.resales-online.com/en/terms-and-conditions.html)

    * It is important to note that the ReSales Online Data Protection Agreement strictly covers the commercial relationship between ourselves and our software subscribers, it does not negate your own data protection responsibilities regarding the collection and protection of the data that you collect from your own clients. If in doubt about your legal responsibilities as a business, we recommend that you seek guidance from a competent source. 

##  **Intellectual property**

The contents, documentation, images, graphics, logos and designs that make up this website (hereinafter corporate elements) are the property of ReSales Andalucia and are duly protected in accordance with the Spanish and International Law on Intellectual Property, for which reason their reproduction or use, in any form, is expressly prohibited without the prior and express authorization of ReSales Andalucia.

Access to this website does not grant users any rights or ownership over the intellectual property rights of the corporate elements other than the uses permitted in the general conditions.

##  **Website content**

All the content of this website and in particular the trademarks, commercial names, industrial designs, designs, texts, photographs, graphics, logos, icons, software or any other signs susceptible of industrial and commercial use are protected by the industrial and intellectual property rights of ReSales Andalucia. Therefore, any use and/or reproduction of the same is prohibited without the express consent of the company.

ReSales Andalucia shall not be liable for the infringement of the intellectual or industrial property rights of third parties that may arise from the inclusion on the website of trademarks, trade names, industrial designs, patents, designs, texts, photographs, graphics, logos, icons or software belonging to third parties who have declared themselves to be the owners of the same when including them on the website.

The user undertakes to use the contents of the website in a diligent, correct and lawful manner and undertakes to refrain from:

  * Using the contents with purposes or effects contrary to law, morality and good customs or public order. 

  * Reproducing, copying, distributing, allowing public access through any form of public communication, transforming or modifying the contents, unless it has the corresponding authorisation from the owner. 

  * Use the contents of the website to send advertising, communications for direct sales purposes or for any other commercial purpose, unsolicited messages addressed to a plurality of persons regardless of their purpose, as well as to refrain from marketing or disclosing such information in any way. 

##  **Telephone Calls**

Telephone calls to and from the offices of ReSales Andalucia are recorded for training and security purposes along with the resolution of any queries arising from the service you receive.

##  **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

##  **Mediation**

In the event of any kind of dispute, both parties will try to come to a friendly agreement. If this is not possible the Courts of MÃ¡laga will have jurisdiction to deal with the case and the parties will not have recourse to any other jurisdiction for the purposes of legal action.

##  **Changes to our Legal Notice & Privacy Policy**

ReSales Andalucia reserves the right to make changes to this Legal Notice & Privacy Policy from time to time and any changes will be posted on this page, so please refer to this page frequently. Your continued use of this website establishes that you accept and agree to any changes to our Privacy Policy.

We may update this policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. If any material changes are made to this Legal Notice & Privacy Policy we will use reasonable endeavours to inform you in advance by email, notice on the Website or other agreed communications channels.
